<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<exercises>
  <exercise>
    <id>0</id>
    <displayId>0</displayId>
    <name>Demographic Survey</name>
    <popupText>This research begins with a demographic survey. Some of the information, 
    such as your career and educational background, are key to the research as they may 
    provide valuable insight into the actions you take during the simulation. Your answers will be kept 
    anonymous through use of a coded ID system. CRCRThank you very much for your participation!
    </popupText>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>1</id>
    <displayId>0</displayId>
    <name>Career Survey</name>
    <popupText>The following questions relate to your career progression. The goal of these questions 
    is to look for a correlation between career progression in particular fields and 
    stronger performance within the game.
    </popupText>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>2</id>
    <displayId>0</displayId>
    <name>Tutorial</name>
    <text>This is the tutorial exercise and introduces you to the game. Use the 
    'Observe' button on the left of the screen to watch the system without moving 
    forward by a turn.
    CRCRClick the 'Change System' button at the bottom of the screen when you are ready to
    advance the system forward and move on to the next turn.</text>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>3</id>
    <displayId>1</displayId>
    <name>Four Shapes</name>
    <text>This is the first real exercise of the game.  Use the 
    Observe and Experiment buttons on the left of the screen to figure out how the system works. 
    CRCRClick the 'Change System' button at the bottom of the screen when you are ready to
    advance the system forward and move on to the next turn.</text>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>4</id>
    <displayId>2</displayId>  
    <usesLevels>true</usesLevels>
    <noSelect>true</noSelect>
    <noDeath>true</noDeath>
    <name>Chaos</name>
    <text>This exercise pulls together the things you've learned about the system in previous 
    exercises.  There are two major changes in this exercise. First, shapes do not divide anymore. 
    Instead, they have a "level" which increases when the shape would have 
    divided previously. The level will appear as a number in the 
    center of the shape when it reaches 1 or higher. Higher level is better.  Secondly, 
    now you only control a single shape. You cannot make changes 
    to other shapes, but you can still change overall system parameters.</text>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>5</id>
    <displayId>0</displayId>
    <name>Feedback Questionnaire</name>
    <popupText>Thank you for playing the game! Your input is extremely valuable. Now we would like you to provide 
    some feedback on your experience.
    CRCRYour feedback will be used to help improve the computer simulation experience and achieve 
    more accurate results in future research.</popupText>
    <!--<popupText>Thank you for playing the game! Your input is extremely valuable. Now that you have finished
    the simulation, there are two more steps.  First, we would like you to provide some feedback on your experience.
    After the feedback, you will be presented with a 16-question Systems Thinking self-assessment. This assessment
    will be used to correlate your simulation results and is key to the research.
    CRCRYour feedback will be used to help improve the computer simulation experience and achieve 
    more accurate results in future research activities.</popupText>-->
  </exercise> 
  <exercise>
    <id>6</id>
    <displayId>0</displayId>
    <name>Systems Thinking Self-Assessment</name>
    <popupText>Thank you for providing your feedback!  As the final step, you will be given a 16-question
    Systems Thinking self-assessment.  Please answer the questions as honestly as possible.  
    CRCRYour results will be correlated with your performance in the simulation and is key to the research.
    CRCRIf you would prefer to do the self-assessment at a later time and you provided your email address for follow-up, 
    you can close the game now.
    </popupText>
  </exercise>
</exercises>