<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<exercises>
  <exercise>
    <id>0</id>
    <displayId>0</displayId>
    <name>Demographic Survey</name>
    <popupText>Before we get started, we just need to ask for some standard 
    demographic information to help with the research. Your answers will be kept 
    anonymous through use of the ID system. CRCRThank you very much for your participation!
    </popupText>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>1</id>
    <displayId>0</displayId>
    <name>Career Survey</name>
    <popupText>Thank you for completing the demographic survey! The information is extremely
    important to the research.CRCR
    The following questions relate to your career progression. The goal of these questions 
    is to determine whether a particular career progression path may lead to a 
    higher level of systems thinking ability.
    </popupText>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>2</id>
    <displayId>1</displayId>
    <name>Practice</name>
    <text>This is the first exercise and introduces you to the platform. It's just a practice 
    exercise so that you can become familiar with the game. Use the 
    'Observe' button on the left of the screen to watch the system without moving 
    forward by a turn.  You have 5 turns to practice.
    CRCRClick the 'Change System' button at the bottom of the screen when you are ready to
    advance the system forward and move on to the next turn.</text>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>3</id>
    <displayId>2</displayId>
    <name>Four Shapes</name>
    <text>This is the first real exercise of the game.  Use the Ask,
    Observe, and Experiment buttons on the left of the screen to figure out how the system works. 
    Keep in mind that you have a limited number of
    Discovery Points to use.  They can all be used on the first turn, or some saved for later turns.
    CRCRClick the 'Change System' button at the bottom of the screen when you are ready to
    advance the system forward and move on to the next turn.</text>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>4</id>
    <displayId>3</displayId>
    <name>Eight Shapes</name>
    <text>This exercise is more complicated than the previous one, introducing additional
    shapes. The systemic knowledge you gained during the previous exercise can be applied
    to this new exercise as the underlying system is the same.</text>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>5</id>
    <displayId>4</displayId>
    <usesLevels>true</usesLevels>
    <noSelect>true</noSelect>
    <noDeath>true</noDeath>
    <name>Chaos</name>
    <text>This exercise pulls together the things you've learned about the system in previous 
    exercises.  There are two major changes in this exercise. First, shapes do not divide anymore. 
    Instead, they have a "level" which increases when the shape would have 
    divided previously. The level will appear as a number in the 
    center of the shape when it reaches 1 or higher. Higher level is better.  Secondly, 
    now you only control a single shape. You cannot make changes 
    to other shapes, but you can still change overall system parameters.</text>
  </exercise>
  <exercise>
    <id>6</id>
    <displayId>0</displayId>
    <name>Post-Assessment Feedback Questionnaire</name>
    <popupText>Thank you for playing the game! Your input is extremely valuable. As the final step,
    we would like you to provide some feedback on your experience.
    CRCRYour feedback will be used to help improve the computer simulation experience and achieve 
    more accurate results in future research activities.</popupText>
  </exercise>
</exercises>