<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<infoList>
    <info name="Welcome">
        <name>Welcome</name>
        <text>
        This game is part of a research project to help define and measure  
        complex problem-solving skills.  In this game, you’ll be asked to observe 
        and interact with a system of shapes and other things that move around the 
        screen and interact with each other.  Your gameplay data will be periodically 
        uploaded to a research server as you play the game.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Introduction">
        <name>Introduction</name>
        <text>
        The purpose of this game is to understand how people approach and solve certain 
        types of complex problems. During the game, you will be presented with a 
        set of scenarios.  In each scenario, there is a system which has a
        set of spinning shapes of various types, colors, sizes, and properties.  The scenario will 
        provide tasks for you to complete, each within a certain number of turns.  
        CRCREach turn is an interval of several seconds during which the system moves forward 
        in time.  Before each turn of the task, you’ll be able to make changes to the system.  
        You’ll also be able to discover information 
        about the system through inquiry, observation, and experimentation. 
        CRCRThe bottom line is, learn about the system, and use that knowledge to change it 
        to do what you want.  CRCRThere are no wrong answers. Just do what you think makes the 
        most sense!  CRCRPlease enjoy!
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="General">
        <name>General</name>
        <text>
        Each scenario consists of several shapes that move around screen and behave in certain ways, 
        some laws that restrict how things work, and other hidden variables.  It will be your job to try 
        to understand how this system works, answer questions about it, and make changes to make it behave 
        certain ways.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Turns">
        <name>Turns</name>
        <text>
        Each turn in the game represents several seconds of time.  Between each turn
        you will have the opportunity to make changes to the system and spend Discovery Points to
        learn more about the system.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Game Play">
        <name>Game Play</name>
        <text>
        The point of this game is to figure out how a system works, and then make changes to make
        it do what you want. To do that, you'll need to know:CRCR
        1: Some things about how the system works.CR
        2: What things you should change.CR
        3: How much to change them (or in which direction).CRCR
        You find out about the system by spending Discovery Points.  Your Discovery Points are
        limited, so take care how you use them.  You won't be able to learn everything about every
        system so you'll have to carefully choose what you want to learn about.  
        </text> 
    </info>
    <info name="Discovery Points">
        <name>Discovery Points</name>
        <text>
        Discovery Points can be used to ask about the system, observe the system in action,
        and experiment with the system.  Your Discovery Points are
        limited, so take care how you use them.  You won't be able to learn everything about every
        system so you'll have to carefully choose what you want to learn about.  CRCRDuring each
        task, you start with a certain number of Discovery Points.  You then gain one
        new Discovery Point each turn.  You do not
        need to spend all of your Discovery Points on the first turn.  You may want to save some to
        use later in the task.  Discovery Points do not carry over between tasks or scenarios.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Ask">
        <name>Ask</name>
        <text>
        Seek textual and numerical facts about the system.  These facts tend to be very precise but
        also very specific.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Observe">
        <name>Observe</name>
        <text>
        Observe how the system behaves over time.  Observations can only be performed starting from
        the default system, before you make any changes.  Thus they cannot be used to precisely predict
        how your changes will affect the system.  But, they can be used to try to figure out how the
        systems works or will work in the absence of any changes.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Experiment">
        <name>Experiment</name>
        <text>
        Devise experiments to test and learn about the system.  You can design an experiment that shows
        how a particular set of changes will affect the system over the course of one turn.  The experiment
        must begin from a known system state; this is to say, either the system in its current state,
        or the system resulting from an experiment.  So it is possible to chain experiments together to
        create interesting sets of behaviors.  
        CRCRWhen creating an experiment, you will be presented with a set of dials, sliders, and selections
        that allow you to tweak the system to your needs.  The options presented during experimentation
        are not necessarily the same as those presented when proceeding to the next turn.
        CRCRNote that you may only have a limited number of experiments in existence
        at any one time.  Once you create an experiment, you can watch and re-watch it as many times as you
        want.  Or, you can delete it to make room for a different experiment.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Change System">
        <name>Change System</name>
        <text>
        Make desired changes to the system, then proceed to the next turn in the task.  Each task has
        only a set number of turns, with a goal that you will be trying to achieve within those turns.
        CRCRWhen proceeding to the next turn, you will be presented with a set of sliders and selections
        that allow you to tweak the system as you wish.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Shapes">
        <name>Shapes</name>
        <text>
        The angled shapes have a certain number of angles, size, color, spin speed, direction, 
        and other attributes.  Some of these attributes affect things strongly, while others have 
        little to no effect.  Try to pay attention to which is which.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Size">
        <name>Size</name>
        <text>
        A shape's size can be roughly equated to its health or success.  Shapes, in general, 
        try to grow larger, with varying degrees of success.  If a shape becomes too 
        small it is destroyed permanently.  If it becomes too large, a shape either splits into
        two smaller shapes, or gains a level, depending on the scenario.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Rain">
        <name>Rain</name>
        <text>
        Small objects that look something like rain can be seen falling from one side of the screen to
        another (usually top to bottom).  Rain has variety of effects when impacting other 
        objects such as spinning shapes, spikes, and circles.  Understanding how the rain affects
        the other parts of the system is important.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Gravity">
        <name>Gravity</name>
        <text>
        Shapes move around the screen based on a property called Gravity.  Try to pay attention to
        how it works and what causes it.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Circles">
        <name>Circles</name>
        <text>
        Circles are created when rain reaches the bottom of the screen.  Each drop of rain
        creates a pair of circles.  Notice how, when two circles collide with each other, 
        they actually create a third circle?  Can this phenomenon be exploited to your advantage?
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Paradigm">
        <name>Paradigm</name>
        <text>
        Depending on the Paradigm chosen, shapes either compete with each other (Competitive), 
        cooperate and work together (Cooperative), or ignore each other and do not interact 
        (Independent).
        </text>
    </info>
</infoList>