<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<infoList>
    <info name="Introduction">
        <name>Introduction</name>
        <text>
        You will be presented a scenario, and given a set of questions.  After the questions, 
        you will be asked to actually take actions on the system to enact changes.  There 
        are no right or wrong answers.  This is simply to determine how you approach different 
        kinds of problems.  Please try your best and answer to the best of your ability. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="General">
        <name>General</name>
        <text>
        This scenario consists of several shapes that move around screen and behave in certain ways., 
        some laws that restrict how things work, and other hidden variables.  It will be your job to try 
        to understand how this system works, answer questions about it, and make changes to make it behave 
        certain ways.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Node">
        <name>Node</name>
        <text>
        A Node is sort of like a self-contained sub-system within the greater system.  
        It has variables and different parts that work together to accomplish tasks, mainly to 
        increase its Success. During this simulation, you will occasionally be given control of Node 1. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Success">
        <name>Success</name>
        <text>
        Success is a general measure of the success of a Node and how well a Node 
        is performing.  It can be "spent" or used to improve or change other parts of the Node. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Entropy">
        <name>Entropy</name>
        <text>
        Entropy is a measure of chaos within a Node.   Entropy consumes Success and can 
        spiral out of control if not carefully monitored and accounted for. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Matter">
        <name>Matter</name>
        <text>
        Nodes use Matter to create things.  Matter is consumed to create Success, 
        and can be used for other purposes such as changes and upgrades to your Node. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Energy">
        <name>Energy</name>
        <text>
        Nodes use Energy to make things happen.  It takes Energy to process Matter into 
        other things like Success.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Knowledge">
        <name>Knowledge</name>
        <text>
        Knowledge helps to prevent Entropy growth, reduces the cost of upgrading, allows 
        for better upgrades, and increases the efficiency of Matter and Energy collection. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Security">
        <name>Security</name>
        <text>
        Security helps defend against theft by other Nodes and attacks from external sources. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Culture">
        <name>Culture</name>
        <text>
        Culture reflects the behavioral traits and beliefs of a Node.  A Node's Culture 
        affects its decision choices and behaviors. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Environment">
        <name>Environment</name>
        <text>
        Environment determines how fast Matter and Energy grow.  However, environment 
        also affects Entropy growth. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Laws">
        <name>Laws</name>
        <text>
        Laws can be implemented to control various parts of the system. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Mindset">
        <name>Mindset</name>
        <text>
        Mindset is the general mindset under which all of the Nodes operate. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Matter Taker">
        <name>Matter Taker</name>
        <text>
        The Matter Taker's purpose is to gather Matter from the Matter Pool.  Unless told 
        otherwise, it will draw as much Matter as it can each turn.  It 
        is able to hold a limited amount of Matter between turns. 
        The Matter Taker has some limits based on its design. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Energy Taker">
        <name>Energy Taker</name>
        <text>
        The Energy Taker's purpose is to gather Energy from the Energy Pool.  Unless told 
        otherwise, it will only draw as much Energy as is needed per turn.  It 
        is not able to hold Energy between turns unless upgraded to do so. 
        The Energy Taker has some limits based on its design. 
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Success Maker">
        <name>Success Maker</name>
        <text>
        The Success Maker takes the Matter and Energy from your Node and turns it 
        into Success.  Generally, the more Matter and Energy you are able to get, the more 
        Success you can make.  
        The Success Maker has some limits based on its design. 
        </text>
    </info>
    
    <info name="Shapes">
        <name>Shapes</name>
        <text>
        The angled shapes have a certain number of angles, size, color, spin speed, direction, 
        and other attributes.  Some of these attributes affect things strongly, while others have 
        little to no effect.  Try to pay attention to which is which.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Size">
        <name>Size</name>
        <text>
        A shape's size can be rougly equated to its health or success.  Shapes, in general, 
        try to grow larger, with varying degrees of success.  If a shape becomes too 
        small it is destroyed permanently.  If it becomes too large, a shape either splits into
        two smaller shapes, or gains a level, depending on the scenario.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Rain">
        <name>Rain</name>
        <text>
        Small objects that look something like rain can be seen falling from one side of the screen to
        another (usually top to bottom).  Rain has variety of effects when impacting other 
        objects such as spinning shapes, spikes, and circles.  Understanding how the rain affects
        the other parts of the system is important.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Gravity">
        <name>Gravity</name>
        <text>
        Shapes move around the screen based on a property called Gravity.  Try to pay attention to
        how it works and what causes it.
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Circles">
        <name>Circles</name>
        <text>
        Circles are created when rain reaches the bottom of the screen.  Each drop of rain
        creates a pair of circles.  Notice how, when two circles collide with each other, 
        they actually create a third circle?  Can this phenomenon be exploited to your advantage?
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="Paradigm">
        <name>Paradigm</name>
        <text>
        Depending on the Paradigm chosen, shapes either compete with each other (Competitive), 
        cooperate and work together (Cooperative), or ignore each other and do not interact 
        (Independent).
        </text>
    </info>
    <info name="System Description">
        <name>System Description</name>
        <text>
        This system consists of spinning shapes, falling rain, small red circles, and spikes.CR
        - Rain falls from the top of the screen towards the bottom.CR
        - When a drop of rain hits a shape, the shape grows.CR
        - When a drop of rain hits the bottom of the screen, it turns into two small circles.CR
        - When a circle hits a shape, the shape grows.CR
        - However, when a drop of rain hits a circle, the circle turns into a spike.CR
        - When a spike hits a shape, the shape shrinks and can be destroyed.CR
        - When a spike hits a circle, the circle is destroyed.CR
        Together these interactions can result a wide variety of situations and phenomena.
        </text>
    </info>
</infoList>